Communications Workers of America Collective Bargaining Agreements 6193
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Communications Workers of America Collective Bargaining Agreements
1971-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Communications Workers of America
CWA
6193
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Collective bargainng agreements.
8247752
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 21, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 30, 2014
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5093: Communications Workers of America, New Jersey Traffic Division #55, CIO and New Jersey Bell Telephone Company Records 5367: New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and Communications Workers of America, New Jersey Traffic Division #55 Records 5120: Southern Bell Telephone and Telegraph Company and the Communications Workers of America. Arbitration Files, ca. 1955.
8247752
- Ameritech, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ameritech, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AT&T, 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AT&T, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AT&T, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- AT&T, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- AT&T, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- AT&T Info Systems, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- AT&T Long Lines, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AT&T Network Systems: Customer Support and Operation, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bell Atlantic, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bell Atlantic Maryland, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bell Atlantic New Jersey, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bell Atlantic Newark Services Group, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- BellSouth, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- BellSouth Advertising and Publishing, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- BellSouth Business Systems, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- BellSouth Communications Systems, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- BellSouth Marketing, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- BellSouth Services, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- BellSouth Telecommunications, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- BellSouth Telecommunications, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- BellSouth Telecommunications, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Bell System Operating Companies, 1973-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Bell Telephone Company of New Jersey, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Bell Telephone Company of Pennsylvania, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Connecticut Union of Telephone Workers and Southern New England Telecommunications, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- GTE California, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- GTE Indiana, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Illinois Bell Telephone Company, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Indiana Bell Telephone Company, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Michigan Bell Telephone Company, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- New England Telephone Company, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone Company, 1971-1989 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- New York Telephone Company, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- North Pittsburgh Telephone, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Northwestern Bell Telephone Company, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Pacific Bell, 1983-1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Pacific Bell, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Pacific/Nevada Bell (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- South Central Bell Telephone Company, 1971-1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Southern Bell, 1971-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, 1983-1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Southwestern Bell Telephone Company, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- United Telephone Company of Ohio, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- US West Clerical/Production and Sales Employees, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- US West Communications, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- US West Communications, 1991-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- US West Communications Market Unit, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- US West Communications Operations, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- US West Contract Training Leaders Guide, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Western Electric, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Wisconsin Bell, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Wisconsin Telephone Company, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- "CWA at Fifty", 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- CWA Telecommunications Industry Bargaining Council Conference on Collective Bargaining, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- E-Mail Correspondence, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- "Labor Market Outcomes of Deregulation in Telecommunications Services", 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- "Summary Data: Entire US Telecommunications Industry" (Box 3, Folder 18)
- "Telecommunications 2004: Strategy, HR Practices, and Performance" (Box 3, Folder 19)